thecasecentre.org 2016-06-13

# Privacy policy | The Case Centre, for educators

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

This policy is limited to the information The Case Centre collects via our websites.

Our website has links to external sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of other sites. 

For the purpose of the [Data Protection Act 1998](http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/1998/29/contents) (the Act), the data controller is The Case Centre.

##  1\. Information we may collect from you

1.1 |  We may collect and process the following data about you:  
---|---  
1.1.1 |  information that you provide by filling in forms on our website (our site).  This includes information provided at the time of registering to use the site, applying to become a member of The Case Centre and seeking or obtaining services from us. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site;  
1.1.2 |  if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;  
1.1.3 |  we may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them;  
1.1.4 |  details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfillment of your orders  
  
##  2\. IP addresses and cookies

2.1 |  We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.  
---|---  
2.2 |  For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us: to estimate our audience size and usage pattern; to store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests; to speed up your searches; and to recognise you when you return to our site.  
2.3 |  The table below explains the cookies we use and why.  
  
**Cookie** |  **Name** |  **Purpose**  
---|---|---  
ColdFusion |  cfide?  
cftoken |  These cookies are essential for running thecasecentre.org as ColdFusion uses them to differentiate requests from different user sessions. The first time a visitor's browser requests a page from thecasecentre.org these cookies are stored on the client machine. Neither of these cookies store any user information; they are purely system generated strings.  
Google Analytics |  _utma _  
_utmb_  
_utmc_  
_utmz |  These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where vistors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. [Click here for an overview of privacy at Google](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)  
  
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

##  3\. Where we store your personal data

3.1 |  The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at **** either of The Case Centre's locations (UK or USA), where staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.  
---|---  
3.2 |  Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology  
3.3 |  Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password that enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  
3.4 |  Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.  
  
##  4\. Uses made of the information

4.1 |  We use information held about you in the following ways:  
---|---  
4.1.1 |  to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;  
4.1.2 |  to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;  
4.1.3 |  to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;  
4.1.4 |  to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;  
4.1.5 |  to notify you about changes to our service;  
4.1.6 |  to process membership queries, applications, renewals and termination; and  
4.1.7 |  to collect all and administer subscriptions.  
4.2 |  If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (email) or post with information about goods and services similar to those that were the subject of a previous sale to you.  
  
##  5\. Communications

5.1 | 

You can subscribe (opt in) to a number of email updates from The Case Centre. You can unsubscribe (opt out) at any time. All the emails you receive will include instructions for unsubscribing.  
  
---|---  
5.2 | 

Our website enables you to email product details to a colleague. You must provide your email address and the email address of the recipient. We use this information to let the recipient know who the email is from, and to trace any email errors in our system. We do not use the information for any other purpose.  
  
##  6\. Disclosure of your information

6.1 | 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in circumstances where we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our website terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of The Case Centre, our members, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
  
---|---  
  
##  7\. Your rights

7.1 |  You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [info@thecasecentre.org](mailto:info@thecasecentre.org).  
---|---  
7.2 |  Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our suppliers and/or customers. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.  
  
##  8\. Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.

##  9\. Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

##  10\. Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [info@thecasecentre.org](mailto:info@thecasecentre.org).
